Guide to the Charles A. Ferguson Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Religious activities, 1956-1987; Series 5
  - International Committee on English in the Liturgy (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Info on the Lutheran Linguist Newsletter (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Works by C. A. Ferguson, 1943-1993; Series 6
- Works by C. A. Ferguson, 1943-1993; Series 6
- Additional material, Accession ARCH-1994-145
  - Language Study Group of Ethiopia (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence and memos, 1969-72 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Elicitation forms (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Central statistical office data (by province) (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Minutes (various meetings), 1967-68 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Directory of Ethiopian Language Specialists, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Word lists, keys, coding instructions, etc. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Working papers, miscellaneous items (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Monograph outlines, classification outlines (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Questionnaires (includes correspondence, memos) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Bibilography of American Indian Language Classification (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Additional material, Accession ARCH-2009-225
  - Whorf, Benjamin Lee – reprints and articles by, 1941-52 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Labov, William – reprints and articles by, 1963-89 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Labov Festschrift – correspondence 1990-91 and drafts of Ferguson’s article (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Additional material, Accession ARCH-2009-263
  - Excerpt from “Short Sketch of the Grammar of the Persian Language” by V. S. Rastorgueva, translated for classroom use by C. A. Ferguson and R. A. C. Goodison, March 1957 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Report: The Ethiopian Language Area, Charles A. Ferguson. July 1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Syllabus [hand-outs?] for History and Civilization of the Middle East, Social Sciences 127, Fall term 1958-59 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Letter to Janet D. Griffith (Center for Applied Linguistics) from D. W. Edwards of Ann Arbor Publishers regarding books available on Persian language, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 4)